I got some salty fries.
Hi.
What's up?
I got a donation.
Couple of donations, so I can drink tonight.
I got butter.
Yeah, thank you so much,
because a couple of people did
see this here.
Oh, it's this guy.
Hi. Hopefully the phone doesn't die.
I'll try to run home.
Let me see. What do I want?
Peach mango? Strawberry lemonade?
An apple coconut. Hell with that. Okay. Hi. Yeah. Hi. Thank you
Yeah, I'm
Can stock it up today?
Lucky day. Say it back, please
So guys, yeah, I got the fries. They're kind of salty, but so good. Thank you. Yep
Yeah, I do pay myself. So I know this is like, you know
My IRL is, like, usually going to McDonald's
and the Wicked Show, but it's IRL.
It is IRL.
Okay.
Hey, did you see Benny?
Benny Blanc, though I saw last night,
he, like, dyed his hair blonde,
because he already bleached it, right?
Thank you, sir.
So, he's got, he's blonde.
I mean, he looks pretty good.
He can pull it off.
I mean, I think I would look kind of,
kind of, like, weird right now if I did blonde hair.
What do you think?
Can I bleach it one day?
Maybe we all bleach it for like a two-day shift.
I don't know.
Oh, hold on.
Do you remember when, oh, sorry.
Remember when Aldi bleached his hair?